HENRIQUE MELO

SKILLS

- Frontend
- HTML CSS JavaScript
- Backend
- PHP · MySQL ·
- WordPress Codex and APIs
- Theme Development
- Divi • Astra • Avada
- Plugin Development
- Advanced Custom Fields (ACF) ·
- Toolset Types
- Form Development
- Contact Form 7 · Gravity Forms ·
- WPForms
- eCommerce Development
- WooCommerce · WP eCommerce ·
- BigCommerce for WordPress

WordPress Expert | CMS Development

RESUME PROFILE

Hi, I am Henrique, a Senior WordPress developer with over 14 years of experience. I developed a wide range of WordPress websites. These websites include general sites, business sites, and eCommerce sites with woo-commerce experience. I customize many WordPress themes using builders like Divi and Elementor.

EXPERIENCE

Senior Wordpress Developer

2022 - Present

Self Employed

Brazil

Company Description

· Which of your achievements match the job you're applying to?

Senior WordPress Developer

02/2020 - 06/2022

Aktie Now

Brazil

Company Description

· Which of your achievements match the job you're applying to?

Wordpress Developer

04/2017 - 06/2020

DBSP

Brazil

Company Description

· Which of your achievements match the job you're applying to?

WordPress Developer

2014 - 2017

Calina Marketing Digital

Brazil

Company Description

• Which of your achievements match the job you're applying to?

WordPress Developer

2011 - 2014

CMA CGM

Brazil

Company Description

• Which of your achievements match the job you're applying to?

Wordpress Developer

2008 - 2011

Sciensa

Brazil

Company Description

• Which of your achievements match the job you're applying to?

Wordpress Developer Certification

2018

WP Academy

Company Description

Which of your achievements match the job you're applying to?

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Computer Science, Computer Engineering

2004 - 2008

Universidade Federal do Rio Grande do Norte